[Music]
Welcome to the program. Sit back in your
seat. Headlines scream at your orders on
repeat. Every channel claims that
they're the only guide. But the more
you're watching, the less you decide.
Scrolling through disasters flash across
the screen. Manufactured panicked in red
and green. Picking sides of profit.
Drama sold as facts. They're keeping us
divided. Never looking back.
Truth decaying
away. The facts get twisted every day.
Truth decay. What can we say when
headlines the racking
[Music]
[Applause]
heads with their agenda set
manufacturing outrage to collect
versus light of false dichotomy
selling fear instead of honesty
[Music]
turn it it off. Tune it out. There's
something better to talk about than
partisan lies. They're shouting out
while the real problems go without.
Truth detailing
away. The facts get twisted every day.
Truth detail. What can we say when
headlines drive the race? Hey
Heat. Heat.
[Applause]
Truth deting away the facts get twisted
every day. Truth DJ, what can we say
when headlines drive the rage? Turn down
the static. Reclaim your head. Start
questioning the narratives you've been
fed. Switch off the circus. Step outside
the frame. Searching for meaning that
isn't just a date. No more distractions.
Break through the haze. Put down the
fear that keeps us all in chains. Build
conversations. Let actions remain. It's
up to us now to spark a change.